Hey, y'all. Can I help you out in here?
Oh, I'm all set, Ben. Gotcha.
Good. I'd go with the rose. That's a good idea.
Today is Diversity Day, and someone's going to come in and talk to us about diversity.
It's something that I've been pushing, that I've been wanting to push for a long time,
and corporate mandated it, and I never actually talked to corporate about it.
They kind of beat me to the punch.
Oh, bastards.
But I was going to, and I think it's very important that we have this.
I'm very, very excited.
That's the thing. It's very sturdy paper, and on the back it says 100% post-consumer content.
What?
Hello?
Uh-huh.
Wait, what?
I'm sorry, Mr. Deckard. I think I'm losing you.
Hello?
Yeah.
Hold on one sec. I don't know. Hold on one second.
Do you really have to do that right now?
Yes, I do. I should have done this weeks ago, actually.
Mr. Deckard, I'm sorry about that.
Can you hold on one second?
Yeah, just one second.
Thanks.
Hello?
Oh, that's it. Perfect.
So, what I was saying...
Hello?
Thanks, Dwight.
Retaliation.
Tit for tit.
That is not the expression.
Well, it should be.
This is my biggest sale of the year.
They love me over there for some reason.
I'm not really sure why, but, you know, I make one call over there every year just to renew their account.
And that one call ends up being 25% of my commission for the whole year.
So, you know, I buy a mini bottle of champagne, celebrate a little.
And this year, I'm pushing recycled paper on them for 1% more.
I don't know. I'm getting cocky, right?
Solitaire?
Yeah. Free sale.
Six on seven.
I know. I saw that.
So, then why didn't you do it?
I'm saving that because I like it when the cards go...
Who doesn't love that?
Hey, Oscar!
How you doing, man?
All right.
Did you have a good weekend going there?
Oh, yeah. I bet it was fun.
Ha, ha, ha!
Oh, hey. This is Oscar.
Martinez.
Right. See? I don't even know. First-name basis.
Great. We're all set.
Oh, hey. Well, diversity, everybody. Let's do it.
Oscar works in here.
Jim, can you wrap it up, please?
Yeah. Mr. Deckard, please?
It's Diversity Day, Jim.
I wish every day was Diversity Day.
You know what? I'm actually going to have to call you back.
Thank you. Sorry about that.
Thank you. Thank you.
Do you want people to come in?
Thank you. Great.
Get in the cars! Get in the cars!
All right. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Okay. Thanks for filling these out, and I promise this will be quick.
At Diversity Today, our philosophy is about honesty and positive expectations.
We believe that 99% of the problems in the workplace arise simply out of ignorance.
You know what? This is a color-free zone here.
Stanley, I don't look at you as another race.
Uh...
See, this is what I'm talking about.
We don't have to pretend that we're colorblind.
Exactly. We're not colorblind.
That's fighting ignorance with more ignorance.
With more intolerance.
No, with more ignorance.
Ignorance.
Right. Exactly.
Instead, we need to celebrate our diversity.
Let's celebrate.
Right. Okay.
Celebrate good times. Come on!
Let's celebrate diversity, right?
Yes, exactly.
Now, here's what we're going to do.
I've noticed that...
You know what? Here's what we're going to do.
Why don't we go around and everybody, everybody,
say a race that you are attracted to sexually.
I will go last.
Go!
I have two.
Nice.
White and Indian.
Actually, I'd prefer not to start that way.
Michael, I would love to have your permission to run this session.
Can I have your permission?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
And it would also help me if you receded.
Okay.
Thank you.
Now, at the start of the session, I'll have you write down an incident
that you found offensive in the workplace.
Now, what I'm going to do is choose one, and we're going to act it out.
Okay, a few other ground rules, just real quick.
Hey, hey, why don't you run it by me, and I'll run it by him?
Okay.
Can we steer away from gay people?
Uh, I'm sorry.
It's an orientation.
It's not a race.
Plus, a lot of other races are also intolerant of gays, so...
Paradox.
Well, we only have an hour.
Okay.
Why don't we just defer...
You'll save time.
Why don't we just defer to Mr., um...
Mr. Brown.
Ah.
All right.
Okay.
First test.
I will not call you that.
Well, it's my name.
It's not a test.
Um...
So, looking through the cards, I've noticed that many of you wrote down the same incident,
which is ironic, because it's the exact incident I was brought in here to respond to.
Now, how many of you are familiar with the Chris Rock routine?
Oh.
Very good.
Okay.
How come Chris Rock can do a routine, and everybody finds it hilarious and groundbreaking,
and then I go and do the exact same routine, same comedic timing, and people file a complaint
to corporate?
Is it because I'm white, and Chris is black?
So, we're going to reenact this with a more positive outcome.
I will play the Chris Rock guy.
Great.
I would like to see someone else pull this off.
Well, let's have someone who wasn't involved in the reenactment.
Okay.
I will play guy listening.
Great.
Guy listening.
Okay.
Uh, anyone else remember?
I remember.
Great.
You're the Chris Rock guy, and you're guy listening.
Okay.
Kevin is a great guy.
He's a great accountant.
He is not much of an entertainer.
Basically, there are two types of black people, and black people are actually more racist
because they hate the other type of black people.
See, every time the one type wants to have a good time, then the other type comes in
and makes a real mess.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
He's ruined.
He's butchering it.
Could you just let me?
Every time.
Every time black people want to have a good time.
They want to have a good time, so I'm going to eat them ass.
I take care of my kids.
They always want credit for something they're supposed to do.
Stop it.
What you want?
A cookie?
Now, this is a simple acronym, HERO.
At Diversity Today, we believe it's very easy to be a hero.
be a hero all you need are honesty empathy respect and open-mindedness
excuse me yeah I'm sorry but that's not all it takes to be a hero oh great well
what is the hero to you a hero kills people people that wish him harm okay a
hero is part human a part supernatural a hero is born out of a childhood trauma
or out of a disaster it must be avenged okay you're thinking of a superhero we
all have a hero in our heart now I need you to take these forms this kind of
expresses the joint experience we had today I want you to look them over and
sign them as kind of a group pledge I
don't think I can find this oh I can't leave until you do well okay I it says
here that I learned something and I knew all this stuff already so I could you
know I could sign something that says that I
talked to my friends I talked to my friends and I talked to myself and I
something or that I helped you teach something so Pam where is she Pam could
we change something on this Michael can I can I talk to you candidly sure we
both know that I'm here because of the comments that you made here's the thing
this office I think is very advanced in terms of racial awareness and it's
probably more advanced than you're used to that's probably throwing you off a
little it's not throwing me I need your signature okay well I know you told me
that well yes but you're not listening to me yours is the only signature I need
okay those are my instructions from the corporate offices to put you through
this seminar for the comments that you made and the only reason why I made
copies for everyone was so that you wouldn't be embarrassed
well here I am thinking that you actually cared about diversity
you
trained in and you don't don't worry about dating okay thank you yep I regret
my actions I regret offending my co-workers I pledged to bring my best
spirit of honesty empathy respect and open-mindedness open-mindedness that
ignored into the workplace and
I'm afraid he'll even start crying then what the fuck is they all going to force
don't really grew up I'm sure those of us here in the words these 어제
duk
will enjoy being a hero sign of the
in this way I can truly be a hero signed daffy duck
he's gonna lose it what he reads that yeah hi mr. Decker in oh well could you
I do believe in that part of the pledge that I just read.
But a pledge? Come on.
I mean, who are we, the Girl Scouts?
No.
Look, the guy, Mr. Brown, he got us halfway there.
He got us talking.
Well, no, I got us talking.
He got us nothing.
He insulted us and he abandoned us.
You call that diversity training?
I don't.
Were there any connections between any of us?
Did anyone look each other in the eye?
Was there any emotion going on?
No.
Where was the heart?
I didn't see any heart.
Where was my Oprah moment?
Okay, get as much done as you can before lunch
because afterward, I'm going to have you all in tears.
Thank you.
All right, everybody pretty.
Come on, here we go.
It's time.
Let's do some good.
Hey, we're not all going to sit in circle Indian style, are we?
Get out.
No, this is not a joke.
Okay?
It was offensive and lame.
So double offensive.
This is an environment of welcoming.
And you should just get the hell out of here.
Okay, let's go.
Let's do it.
Come on, let's have some fun, everybody.
Here we go.
Take a seat.
Cop a squat.
And thank you for coming in.
Diversity is the cornerstone of progress, as I've always said.
But don't take my word for it.
Let's take a look at the tape.
Hi, I'm Michael Scott.
I'm in charge of Dunder Mifflin Paper Products here in Scranton, Pennsylvania.
But I'm also the founder of Diversity Tomorrow, because today is almost over.
Abraham Lincoln once said that if you're a racist, I will attack you with the north.
And those are the principles that I carry with me in the workplace.
Okay, questions, comments?
Anybody?
Jim?
Is that it?
Yes.
I only had an hour to put it together, but I'm going to add on to it later on.
It was kind of hard to hear.
Yes.
That probably had something to do with the camera work.
Anybody else?
I have a customer meeting.
Yeah, well, if you leave, we'll only have two left.
Yes.
Enjoy.
Absolutely.
Namaste.
Okay, well, since I am leading this...
Let's get down to business, and why don't I just kind of introduce myself, okay?
I am Michael, and I am part English, Irish, German, and Scottish.
Sort of a virtual United Nations.
But what some of you might not know is that I am also part Native American Indian.
What part Native American?
Two-fifteens.
That fraction doesn't make any sense.
Well...
You know what?
It's kind of hard for me to talk about.
They're suffering.
So who else?
Let's get this popping.
Come on.
Who's going?
Let's go here.
Oscar, right here.
You're on.
Okay, Michael.
Both my parents were born in Mexico.
Oh, yeah.
And they moved to the United States a year before I was born.
Yeah.
So I grew up in the United States.
Wow.
And my parents were Mexican.
That is a great story.
Hey, that's the American dream right there, right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Let me ask you, is there a term besides Mexican that you prefer?
Something less offensive?
Mexican isn't offensive.
Well, it has certain connotations.
Like what?
Like...
I don't...
Well, I don't know.
Well, what connotations, Michael?
No, no, no.
It must have meant something.
No.
Now, remember...
I'm just curious.
Honesty.
Yeah.
Empathy.
Respect.
Jim?
Hello?
I have something here.
I want you to take a card.
Put it on your...
Don't look at the card.
I want you to take the card, and I want you to put it on your forehead.
And...
Take a card.
Any card.
And I want you to treat other people like the race that is on their forehead.
Okay?
So everybody has a different race.
Nobody knows what their race is.
So I want you to really go for it, because this is real.
You know, this isn't just an exercise.
This is real life, and I have a dream that you will really let the sparks fly.
Get her done.
Why?
Because Martin Luther King is a hero of mine.
There's this great Chris Rock bit about how streets named after Martin Luther King tend
to be more violent.
I'm not going to do it, but it's...
Oh, this is a good one.
Um, hi.
How are you?
Fine.
Push it.
Great.
Um...
I admire your culture's success in America.
Thank you.
Good.
Bum, bum, ba-bum, bum.
Come on.
Olympics of suffering right here.
Slavery versus the Holocaust.
Come on.
What am I supposed to be?
It's going to percolate.
No, no, no.
Well, that...
That was inadvertent.
We didn't actually plan that.
Lots of cultures eat rice.
It doesn't help me.
Never say.
Um, Shalom.
I'd like to apply for a loan.
That's nice.
Dwight.
Okay, do me.
Something stereotypical, so I can get it really quick.
Okay.
I like your food.
Um, Outback Steakhouse.
I'm Australian, mate.
Pam.
No.
Come on.
I like your food.
No.
Come on.
Stir the pot.
Stir the melting pot.
Bam.
Let's do it.
Let's get ugly.
Let's get real.
Okay.
If I have to do this based on stereotypes that are totally untrue, that I do not agree
with, I will.
not agree with you would maybe not be a very good driver oh man am i a woman you'll notice i didn't
have anybody be an arab i thought that would be too explosive but uh no pun intended but i just
thought too soon for arabs maybe next year um you know the ball's in their court what are you
watching chappelle show really yeah i downloaded it on her computer i hope she doesn't mind she
just had a lot of extra no way no i think she really likes this stuff great she's cute huh
yeah you know she's engaged but oh no the girl in the sketch oh yeah she's hot yeah
hey hey you want to go to the beach sure you want to get high no
i think you do mon stop okay all right no all right that's good
okay all right no all right that's good okay all right no all right that's good
you just you need you need to push it you know you need to go a little bit further
oh all right what okay kelly how are you i just had the longest meeting oh welcome to my
convenience store would you like some googie googie oh i have some very delicious googie googie
only 99 cents plus tax try my googie googie try my googie googie try my googie googie try my
all right all right yes that was great she gets it now she knows what it's like to be a minority
mr deckard we didn't lose your sale today did we excellent okay let me just get your
what's that no we didn't we didn't close last time i just need your uh
oh what what code were you given
oh okay yeah no that's actually another salesman here yeah i can redo it if you want to do that
oh we give you a discount no i don't blame you i just hated it when that guy was in here
mr brown if that was his real name i mean he had a lot of money and he had a lot of money
he'd never met any of us before and here he was telling us how to do our thing
i just wanted i just wanted to do it our way you know on our own
man i should have gotten some food maybe some spaghetti okay kevin you can take off that thing
okay that would really really shown him up wouldn't it i'd brought in some burritos or some
colored greens or some pad thai i love pad thai it's collard greens what it's collard greens
uh it doesn't really make sense because you don't call them collard people that's offensive
okay well it's after five so thank you very much buena vista oscar thank you good job
oh my man
thank you brazil nice
hey we can go
um
um not a bad day
yeah
you