all right jim your quarterlies look very good how are things going at the library
oh i told you i couldn't close it so so you've come to the master for guidance
is this what you're saying grasshopper uh actually you called me in here but yeah all right well let
me show you how it's done yes i'd like to speak your office manager please yes hello this is
michael scott i am the regional manager of dunder mifflin paper products just wanted to talk to you
manager a manager all right done deal thank you very much sir you're a gentleman and a scholar
oh i'm sorry okay i'm sorry my mistake
that was a woman i was talking to
so she had a very low voice probably a smoker so
so that's the way it's done i've uh i've been at dunder mifflin for 12 years the last four as
regional manager uh when i come through here see we have the entire floor so this is my kingdom
far as the eye can see ah this is our receptionist pam pam pam pam
isley uh pam has been with us um for forever right pam well i don't know if you think she's
cute now you should have seen her a couple of years ago what uh any messages um yeah just a
fax oh pam this is from corporate how many times have i told you that there's a special
filing cabinet for things from corporate you have called the white paper basket
look at that
god oh look at that face people say i am the best boss they go god we've never worked in a place
like this before you're hilarious and you get the best out of us um i think that pretty much sums it
up i found it at spencer gifts
um
I have no gifts for you
my job is to speak to clients um on the phone about uh quantities and uh type of
copy or paper you know uh whether we can supply it to them whether they can uh
uh pay for it and uh
um
I I'm boring myself just talking about this
what's up
I still love that after seven years
urggh wow
eh
ah
what nothing okay all right see you later all right
take care back to work
um i don't know just before lunch that was great corporate really doesn't interfere with me at all
um jan levinson gould hello yeah i call her hillary rodham clinton right not to her face
because uh well not because i'm scared of her because i'm not but um yeah all right was there
anything you wanted to add to the agenda me no get an agenda i'm what i'm sorry i didn't get any
agenda well i faxed one over to you this morning really because i didn't uh i didn't did we get a
you
fax this morning uh yeah the one did that why why is it in my hand because the company runs
on efficiency of communication right um so what's the problem pam why i didn't uh why don't you get
it you put it in the garbage can that was a special filing cabinet
yeah uh that was a joke that was a joke that uh was actually my brother's and it was it was
supposed to be with bills and it doesn't work great with faxes you want to look at mine yeah
yeah i would thanks okay since the last meeting alan and the board have decided that we can't
justify a scranton branch and a stanford branch oh okay no michael no no no no no no this is good
this is good this is fine listen okay don't panic all the alarm bells are kind of going
i've spoken to josh and stanford i've told him the same as you and it's up to either you or him
to convince me that your branch can incorporate the other okay no problem this does however mean
that there's going to be downsizing
me no want to hear that jan because downsizing is a bitch it is a real bitch and i wouldn't uh
wish that on josh's men i certainly wouldn't wish it on my men or women present company excluded
sorry uh is josh concerned about downsizing himself not downsizing himself but is he
concerned about downsizing
question how long do we have to act
oh uh todd packer terrific rep do you mind if i take it
hackman hey big queen oh that's not appropriate
um i don't know i don't know what you mean look i've been here to ask her one
uh question does the carpet match the drape oh my god oh that's horrifying
i'm a horrible horrible person
so do you think we could keep a lid on this for now i don't want to worry people unnecessarily
no absolutely under this regime it will not leave this office just like that so what does
downsizing actually mean well you guys gotta update your resumes just like i'm doing i bet
it's gonna be me probably gonna be me yeah it'll be you i have an important question for you yes
oh are you going to angela's camp party on sunday yeah stop
that is ridiculous am i going to tell them no i'm not going to tell them i don't see the point of that
as a doctor you would not tell a patient if they had cancer hey hey this is mr scott guilty
ryan uh howard from the temp agency uh-huh daniqua sent me down to start today howard
like uh mo howard three stooges yep watch this this is mo
uh right here three stooges high five oh pam it's a guy thing
pam i'm sort of a student of comedy watch this
i'm hitler adolf hitler
i don't think it would be the worst thing if they let me go because then i might i just i
don't think it's many little girls dream to be a receptionist um i like to do illustrations
um mostly watercolor a few oil pencil um jim thinks they're good dunder mifflin this is pam
sure uh mr davis let me call you right back yeah something just came up two minutes
thank you very much what are you doing what what are you doing just clearing my desk i can't
concentrate it's not on your desk it's overlapping it's all filling over the edge one word two
syllables demarcation
you can't do that why not safety violation i could fall and pierce an organ we'll see
this is why the whole downsizing thing just doesn't bother me downsizing downsizing yeah i
have no problem with that i have been recommending downsizing since i've
first got here i even brought it up in my interview i say bring it on
you just still have these messages from yesterday relax everything's under control
uh yeah oh yeah yeah oh that's important right oh this is so important i should run to answer it
shut the
door
shut the door
shh
shut
6 million man
steve austin actually that
would be a good salary for me don't you think
six million dollars memo to jan i deserve a raise
don't we all i'm sorry
that's nothing
if you're unhappy with your compensation
maybe you should take it up with HR, okay?
Not today, okay?
Pam, just be professional.
I think I'm a role model here.
I think I garner people's respect.
Attention all Dunder Mifflin employees, please.
We have a meeting in the conference room.
ASAP.
People I respect, heroes of mine, would be Bob Hope,
Abraham Lincoln, definitely, Bono, and probably God would be the fourth one.
And I just think all those people really helped the world in so many ways that it's
really important.
It's really beyond words.
It's really incalculable.
Now, I know there's some rumors out there, and I just kind of want to set the record straight.
I'm assistant regional manager.
I should know first.
Assistant to the regional manager.
Okay.
Can you just tell me, please?
Just tell me quietly.
Well, I'm about to tell everybody.
Can you whisper it in my ear?
I'm just about to tell everyone.
Can't you just tell us?
Please.
Okay.
Do you want me to tell them?
You don't know what it is.
Can you tell them, with my permission?
I don't need your permission.
Permission granted.
Go ahead.
Corporate has deemed it appropriate.
To enforce an ultimatum upon me.
And Jan is thinking about downsizing either the Stanford branch or this branch.
I heard they might be closing this branch down.
That's just...
That's just a rumor going around.
This is my first day.
I don't really know.
Yeah, but Michael, what if they downsize here?
Not gonna happen.
It could be out of your hands, Michael.
It won't be out of my hands, Stanley, okay?
I promise you that.
Oh, can you promise that?
On his mother's grave.
Well...
No.
Well, yeah, it is a promise.
And frankly, I'm a little bit insulted that you have to keep asking about it.
It's just that we need to know.
Yeah, absolutely.
I know.
I...
Hold on a second.
I think Pam wanted to say something.
Pam?
You, uh, had a look that you wanted to ask a question just then?
I was in the meeting with Jan, and she did say that it could be this branch that gets the ax.
Are you sure about that?
Well, Pam?
Maybe you should stick to the ongoing confidentiality agreement of meetings.
Pam, information is power, so...
So you can't say for sure whether it's gonna be us or them, can you?
No, no, no, no, Stanley.
No, you did not see me in there with her.
I said, if, uh, if corporate wants to come in here and interfere, then they're gonna have to go through me, right?
You know, you can go mess with Josh's people, but I'm the head of this family, and, uh, you ain't gonna be messing with my children.
If I left, what would I do with all this useless information in my head, you know?
Tonnage price of manila folders?
Um, Pam's favorite flavor of yogurt, which is mixed berry.
Jim said mixed berries?
Oh, wow.
Yeah, he's on to me.
Um...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, watch out for this guy, Dwight Schrute in the building.
This is Ryan, the new temp.
What's up?
Nice to meet you.
Introduce yourself, be polite.
Uh, Dwight Schrute, assistant regional manager.
Assistant to the regional manager.
So, uh, Dwight, tell him about the, uh, the kung fu and the, uh, car and everything.
Uh, yeah, I got a, uh, 78 280Z.
I bought it for 1,200, fixed it up, so now we're at three grand.
That is his profit.
Yeah.
Uh, new engine, suspension, I got a re-spray, I got some photos.
Oh!
Damn it!
Damn!
Okay.
Hold on, hold on.
Judge is in session.
What is the problem here?
He put my stuff in Jell-O again.
That's real professional.
Thanks.
This is the third time, and it wasn't funny the first two times either, Jim.
All right, all right.
It's okay here.
Uh, but people sometimes take advantage because it's so relaxed.
I'm a volunteer sheriff's deputy on the weekends, and you cannot screw around there.
That's sort of one of the rules.
Yeah.
What is that?
That's my staple.
No, no, no, no!
Do not take it out.
You have to eat it out of there, because there are starving people in the world, and, which
I hate, and it is a waste of that kind of food.
Okay, you know what?
You can be a witness.
Can you reprimand him, please?
How do you know it was me?
It's always you.
Are you gonna discipline him or not?
Ooh, discipline.
Kinky.
All right.
Here's the deal, you guys.
The thing about a practical joke is that you have to know when to start as well as when
to stop.
And, yeah.
And, Jim, now is the time to stop putting Dwight's personal effects into jello.
Okay.
Dwight, I'm sorry, because I've always been your biggest flan.
Oh, nice!
That's the way it is around here.
Just kind of go around and around and around.
You should have put him in custody.
Oh, hey!
Yes!
New guy!
And he scores!
Okay, that's great.
I guess what I'm most concerned with is damage to company property.
That's all.
Pudding.
I'm trying to think of another dessert to do.
Do you like going out at the end of the week for a drink?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, that's why we're all going out.
So that we can have an end-of-the-week drink.
So when are we going out?
I don't know.
Tonight.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hey, man.
Hey.
What's going on?
Hi, baby.
Hey.
Roy's my fiancé.
We've been engaged about three years, and we were supposed to get married in September,
but I think we're going to get married in the spring.
Do you mind if I go out for a drink with these guys?
No.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Go home.
Okay.
I'm going to be a few minutes away.
It's only twenty past five.
I still have to do my faxes.
You know what?
You should come with us, because, you know, we're all going out, and it could be a good
chance for you to see what people are like outside of the office.
You know, I think it could be fun.
No.
It sounds good.
Oh, no.
Seriously, we got to get going.
Yeah.
the vibe yet we work hard we play hard sometimes we play hard and we should be
working hard right I guess the the atmosphere that I've created here is
that I'm a friend first and a boss second probably yeah entertainer third
just a second right oh hey do you uh do you like the Jamie Kennedy experiment
and pumped and all that kind of stuff okay you were gonna be my accomplice
just go along with it okay all right just follow my lead don't pimp me all
right come in so corporate just said that I don't want to oh thank you Pam
can you come in here for a second let's have a seat I was gonna call you in
anyway you know Ryan um as you know there is going to be downsizing and you
have made my life so much easier in that I am going to have to let you go first
you
what why why well theft and stealing stealing um what what am I supposed to
have stolen post-it notes post-it notes what are those worth like 50 cents 50
cents yeah you steal a thousand post-it notes at 50 cents apiece and you know
you've made a profit margin you know go run us out of business Pam are you
serious
yeah
I am um I can't believe this I mean I've never even stolen as much as a
paperclip and now you're firing me but the best thing about it is that uh we're
not gonna have to give you any severance pay because that is gross misconduct and
uh they'll just clean out your desk I'm sorry
foreign
you've been
drunk surprise it's a joke we were joking around see okay he was in on it he was my
accomplice and there was just kind of a morale booster thing and we were showing the new guy
around kind of kind of giving him the feel of the place so you should God you were we totally got
you're a jerk I don't know about that
um
isolated
thing for a company is it the cash flow is it the inventory
it's the people the people my proudest moment here was not when I increased profits by 17
or when I cut expenses without losing a single employee no no no
it was a young Guatemalan guy first job in the country barely spoke English came
to me and said mr. Scott would you be the godfather of my child didn't work
out in the end we had to let him go he sucked hey hey hey how are you good I
thought you were going out for a drink with oh no how's your headache it's
better good is uh yeah um are you uh my walking out yes
yes I do you wanna yeah right great let me just oh Roy yeah listen have a nice
weekend yeah definitely you too enjoy it
you know
you